- 드레이크!
- 미안해, 앰버
-Oh, Drake.
-I'm sorry, Amber.
이 말은 브래드가 해야 했지만
It's like Brad to have
to have the last word.
Sorry I'm late.
What happened?
늦어서 미안
어떻게 됐어?
거의 끝나 가
We wanna see the end.
- 당신을 원해요, 드레이크
- 나도 알아
I want you, Drake.
I know you do.
하지만 우린 운명적으로
만날 수 없어
But we can never
be together that way.
뭐예요?
What?
밝힐 게 있어, 난 사실...
There's something I never told you.
I'm actually your half-brother.
네 오빠야
그래서 어떻게 돼?
So what happens next?
난 샴쌍둥이 분리수술로
의학상을 받고
I get the medical award
for separating the Siamese twins.
앰버와 쌍둥이 형 라몬을
찾아서 베네수엘라로 떠나
Then Amber and I go to Venezuela
to meet our other half-brother, Ramon...
거기서 세계 최대의 에메랄드를
발견하는데 그게 저주받은 거야
...where I find the world's
biggest emerald. It's really big.
But it's cursed.
So cool!
정말 유익한 프로구나
God, that is good TV!
The One Where Dr. Ramoray Dies
- 피비 같이 하자
- 싫어
Pheebs, play with me!
게임이 너무 망측해
This game is grotesque!
팔도 없는 불쌍한 남자들의
허리에 쇠창살을 끼워?
Twenty armless guys joined
at the waist by a steel bar...
그리고 평생 축구만 시키지?
...forced to play soccer forever?
Hello? Human rights violation!
완전히 인권침해야
피비, 기분 나빠할 것 없어
Don't feel so bad.
After playing...
경기 끝나면 여자 인형을 넣어서
재미보게 할 거라고
...I break out the plastic women
and everybody has a good time.
Why don't you play with your roommate?
네 룸메이트랑 하지 그래?
축구가 별로인가 봐
He's not a big fan of foosball.
Are we not getting along
with the new boy?
우리랑 어울리지도 않겠대?
아냐, 괜찮은 친군데
주로 방에만 틀어박혀 있어
No, he's all right. He spends
most of his time in his room.
That's because you haven't
gotten to know him.
네가 친해지려는 노력을
안 해서겠지
Let's remedy that, shall we?
구제해 주자
- 구제는 무슨...
- 재미있을 거야
-We don't need to.
-lt'll be fun!
What was that?
뭐야?
안녕, 우리 맥주 마시면서
인사나 나누면 어떨까?
I thought it'd be fun if we had
beers and got to know each other.
All right.
- 그래, 그러지 뭐
- 좋았어!
Oh, good! Okay.
Oh, no! I have to go,
because I'm late for...
그런데 난 가 봐야 돼
'무공해 달걀과 햄'
토론회가 있거든
... my Green Eggs and Ham
discussion group.
오늘 밤 주제는 '기차에서
그걸 먹으면 왜 안 되나'야
Tonight, it's "Why he would not
eat them on a train."
-Have fun! Bye!
-That was so lame.
재미있게 놀아, 잘 있어
- 너무 어색했어
- 알아
I know.
말시켜 봐
Okay, talk to him.
So you think that Speed Racer guy
gets a lot of tickets or...?
저기... 자동차 레이서는
딱지를 많이 뗄까, 아닐까?
재미있다, 그래서
누가 누구랑 깨졌다는 거야?
That's good.
So who broke up with who?
뭐 들었어?
내가 여자랑 헤어졌다니까
I broke up with her.
She actually thought Sean Penn
was the capital of Cambodia.
숀 팬이 캄보디아의
수도인 줄 알더라고
When everybody knows that
the capital of Cambodia is....
그 정도는 삼척동자도 알겠다
캄보디아의 수도는...
- 숀 팬은 아냐
- 맞아
It's not Sean Penn.
I got a funny one.
웃긴 얘기 하나 하지
My last girlfriend, Tilly.
We're eating breakfast, right?
전 여자친구 이름이 틸리였어
매일 아침 내가 팬케이크를
만들어 줬는데 50개가 되던 날
I made these pancakes.
Like, 50 pancakes.
All of a sudden,
she turns to me and says, "Eddie...
대뜸 날 보면서 이러잖아
'에디, 더 이상 널 보기 싫어'
... I don't wanna see you anymore."
It was literally like she had
reached into my chest...
그 말이 내 가슴을 갈라서
심장을 도려내 내던진 듯했어
... ripped out my heart
and smeared it all over my life!
난 절망의 구렁텅이에 빠져
영원히 헤어나지 못할 것 같아
There was this incredible abyss
and I'm falling.
I keep falling and
I don't think I'm ever gonna stop!
That wasn't such a funny story.
그리 웃긴 얘긴 아니었지?
괴팍한 노인이 말하길
'난 할 수 있는 것만 하겠어'
And a crusty old man
Said I'll do what I can
그러자 쥐들이 신나게
악기를 연주했네
And the rest of the rats
Played maracas
That's it! Thanks! Good night.
감사합니다
잘 가요
Phoebe's got another job, right?
피비 본업은 따로 있겠지?
Great set tonight, Pheebs.
- 피비, 잘했어
- 나도 알아
I know.
We should get going.
우리는 가야겠어
We should too.
I've got patients at 8 in the morning.
우리도 가야 해
아침 일찍 환자랑 약속했거든
있잖아요
늘 자기 집에만 갔으니까
You know how we always stay
at your apartment?
I thought tonight
we'd stay at my place.
오늘은 우리 아파트로
가는 게 좋겠어요
I don't know.
I don't have my jammies.
글쎄, 파자마도 없잖아
그런 건 필요 없어요
You don't need them.
My baby sister, ladies and gentlemen.
제 철없는 동생이랍니다
신사숙녀 여러분
Shut up. I'm happy.
분위기 깨지 마
Oh, this is so nice!
I have to make a speech.
정말 보기 좋다
내가 한마디 할게
Of all the guys that Monica has
been with, and that is a lot...
모니카가 사귀던 그 수많은
남자들 중에 말이야
...I like you the best.
그중에 당신이 최고예요
Thank you, Pheebs.
That's very sweet.
고마워, 피비
기분 좋은데
내가 최고라는군
You hear that?
She likes me best. And apparently,
there have been a lot.
그 많은 남자들 중에서 말야
많긴요, 농담하는 거예요
정신이 오락가락하거든요
Not a lot.
Phoebe's kidding. Phoebe's crazy.
Phoebe's dead.
피비는 죽었다
- 안녕하세요?
- 안녕하세요
I'm looking for Eddie Manoick.
에디를 보러 왔어요
He's not here right now.
I'm Chandler.
지금 없어요
말 전해 줄까요?
아님 어항이라도
Can I take a message or....
Or a fish tank?
- 고마워요
- 들어와요
Thanks.
Come on in.
I'm Tilly.
전 틸리라고 해요
I gather by that "Oh,"
he told you about me.
제 얘기를 했었나 보군요
Yeah, your name came up...
어쩌다 튀어나왔어요
...in a conversation that
terrified me to my very soul.
무지하게 무서운 얘기였죠
에디가 좀 감정적이죠?
He's kind of intense.
Yes! Hey, can I ask you,
is Eddie a little...
그래요, 물어 볼 게 있는데
에디가 약간...
- 약간 뭐?
- 왕 촌스럽죠?
A little what?
...bit country?
Come on in, you roomie!
이제 오니, 룸메이트?
Hello, Tilly.
안녕, 틸리?
Eddie, I just came by
to drop off your tank.
네 어항 갖다주러 들렀어
눈물나게 고맙다
That was very thoughtful of you.
눈물이 나
It's very thoughtful.
Well, okay then.
그럼 이만 갈게
I'm gonna go. Bye.
- 잘 있어
- 잘 가
잘 가요
So we getting a fish?
이제 물고기 키우게 생겼네
너 틸리랑 잤지?
You had sex with her.
피비, 이것 봐
Check it out, check it out!
'TV 가이드'구나
내가 제일 좋아하는 책이야
Soap Opera Digest!
That's one of my favorite digests!
Page 42! Page 42!
- 42페이지를 펴 봐
- 알았어
'우리들의 삶'의 새로운 의사
조이 트리비아니
"New Doc on the Block,
Days of our Lives Joey Tribbiani."
사진 잘 나왔는데!
Cool picture!
역시 멋있어
Oh, I look good.
Is this true? That you write
a lot of your own lines?
네가 네 대사를 쓴다는
이 말이 사실이니?
Well, kind of, yeah.
어느 정도는...
Remember last week
when Alex was in the accident?
지난주에 알렉스가
사고 당한 거 생각나?
The line in the script was...
마지막 대사가 '병원으로
안 옮기면 죽을 겁니다'인데
... "If we don't get this woman
to a hospital, she's going to die."
But I made it, "If this woman
doesn't get to a hospital...
내가 바꿨어, '병원에 안 가면
살 수 없을 겁니다'로
...she's not gonna live."
Oh, okay.
I see what you did there.
뭔지 알겠어
Aren't you afraid the writers will be
kind of mad when they read this?
작가가 이걸 보면
펄쩍 뛸 텐데 걱정 안 돼?
I never thought about the writers.
The scripts just come to my house.
작가를 생각해 본 적이 없어
대본은 배달되거든
But you know what?
하지만 생각해 봐
This makes me look good,
which makes the show look good...
내 이미지를 살리는 길이
곧 드라마를 살리는 길이고
...which makes the writers look good.
So how could they be mad?
그래야 작가들이 먹고 살지
Makes up most of his lines.
멋대로 대사를 바꿔?
이 나쁜...
Son of a....
두고 보자, 멍청한 녀석...
Write this, jerk-weed.
엘리베이터 통로로 떨어져요?
I fall down an elevator shaft?
What does this mean?
무슨 뜻이죠?
제가 떨어지다뇨?
몰라요
전 배달만 하거든요
I don't know.
I just bring the scripts.
They can't kill me!
I'm Francesca's long-lost son!
날 죽일 순 없어요!
난 프란체스카의 아들인데!
Right.
그럼요
- 서명해 주시겠어요?
- 싫어요
Could you sign?
No! No way! I'm not signing that!
절대 안 돼요
난 서명 못해 줘요
서명한다고 줄거리가
바뀌는 건 아닐 텐데요?
I don't think that will affect
the plot of the show.
How can they do this to me?
어떻게 나한테 이럴 수가 있죠?
전 그만 가 볼게요
All right, I'm just gonna go.
미안해요
Sorry.
많다는 건 말이 안 돼요
세상에 남자가 얼마나 많은데
Well, it wasn't that many guys.
If you consider how many guys
there actually are...
...it's a very small percentage.
그에 비하면 극소수라구요
문제 삼자는 게 아냐
그냥 궁금해
It's not that big a deal.
I was just curious.
- 잘 자
- 잘 자요, 리차드
-Good night.
-Good night, Richard.
행운을 빌어, 모니카
Good luck, Mon.
좋아요, 먼저 당신은
몇 명이었는지 말해 봐요
Before I tell you, you tell me
how many women you've been with.
Two.
두 명
Two? Two?
둘? 두 명이라구요?
How is that possible? I mean...
그게 가능해요?
당신같이 멋진 남자가?
... have you seen you?
어떻게 말해야 되나?
I mean, what can I say?
고등학교 때 만난 바바라와
결혼해서 30년을 살았어
I was married to Barbara for 30 years,
my high-school sweetheart.
그 다음에 당신을 만났지
그래서 둘이야
Now you. That's two.
Two it is.
그럼 둘 맞네
Time for bed.
I'm gonna brush my teeth.
잘 시간이에요
양치하러 가야지
잠깐, 당신 차례잖아
No, wait a minute now!
Come on, it's your turn.
Oh, come on!
You know, I don't need the
actual number. Just a ballpark.
그럼 확실한 숫자 말고
대강만 얘기해 봐
Okay, it is definitely
less than a ballpark.
좋아요
야구장은 못 채워요
I am so glad
I'm not Monica right now.
이럴 때는 모니카가 아닌 게
얼마나 다행인지 몰라
Tell me about it.
그럼
그건 그렇고 몇 명이었어?
So what's your magic number?
Come on, you know everyone
I've been with. All both of them.
내가 누구랑 사귄진 다 알잖아
전부 해봐야 둘이지만
그러니까... 자기가 있고
Well, there's you.
순서대로 말할 필요는 없어
Better not be doing these in order.
빌리 드레스킨, 피트 카니...
Billy Dreskin, Pete Carny.
Barry.
배리 그리고... 파올로!
Paolo.
Oh, yes, the weenie from Turinie.
토리니에서 온 약골?
파올로를 질투하는 거야?
Honey, are you jealous of Paolo?
I'm so much happier with you
than I ever was with him.
그 때와는 비교도 안 될 정도로
난 지금 행복해
-Really?
-Oh, please!
- 진짜?
- 그럼
That Paolo thing was
barely a relationship.
팔로와는 교감이란 게 없었어
순전히 의미 없는
동물적인 결합이었지
All it really was
was just meaningless, animal sex.
Okay, you know, that sounded
so much better in my head.
그것도 아주 잘 평가한 거야
I didn't sleep with
your ex-girlfriend.
난 네 옛날 여자친구와 안 잤어
정말 우습군, 그녀와 잤던
놈들은 다 그렇게 말했어
That's exactly what someone
who slept with her would say.
This is nuts! Crazy!
She came over for two minutes...
그건 억지야, 미치겠군
2분 동안 어항을 놓고 간 게
다였다구!
...dropped off a fish tank and left!
Where's Buddy?
- 버디는 어디 있어?
- 버디?
Buddy?
내 금붕어 버디 말이야
My fish, Buddy.
There was no fish
when she dropped it off.
금붕어는 안 놓고 갔어
말도 안 돼, 없다고?
This is unbelievable!
내 여자친구랑 자고
거짓말로 내 추리력을 모독했어
You sleep with my ex-girlfriend,
insult my intelligence by lying...
...then you kill my fish?
My Buddy?
그것도 모자라서
내 금붕어를 죽여?
죽이지 않았다니까!
이봐, 에디!
I didn't kill your fish!
Look, Eddie
Would you look at what I'm doing?
내가 어떻게 할 건지 볼래?
이건 현명한 처사가 아니지
Now that can't be smart.
So we're just gonna
take this guy right off you...
그러니까 요 녀석을 떼어서
주머니 속에 처넣자고
...and put him here in Mr. Pocket.
이거 먹을래?
Tangelo?
그게 다야? 고작 그런 것 가지고
말 안 했단 말야?
That's it? That's the giant number
you were afraid to tell me?
- 네
- 많은 것도 아니잖아
Well, that's not bad at all.
난 일개 소대쯤 될 줄 알았지
You had me thinking it was,
like, a fleet.
정말 괜찮아요?
You're okay with it?
- 난 아무렇지도 않아
- 잘됐네요
Oh, honey, I'm fine.
그 '둘' 말인데요
Okay, about that two.
뭐?
What?
그 '둘'이 뭐?
All right.
What about my two?
- 너무 적은 수잖아요
- 맞아, 그런데?
It just seems like
a really small number.
Right.
재미 삼아 바람피울
생각도 안 해봤어요?
Don't you have a lot
of wild oats to sow?
혹시 지금 바람피우는 건가요?
날 장난감으로 생각하죠?
Or is that what you're doing with me?
Oh, my God! Am I an oat?
그렇지 않아, 내 말은...
Honey, you are not an oat.
난 적어도 바람둥이는 아냐
사랑하는 사람하고만 잔다고
I don't know, I guess
I'm just not an oat guy.
I've only slept with women I love.
You've only slept with two people.
겨우 두 명하고만 잤잖아요?
그래
Right.
이럴 수가...
저도 당신을 사랑하는 거 알죠?
You know I love you too, right?
응, 알아
Now I do.
로스!
로스, 내 말을 들어 봐
Ross, please listen to me.
자기는 파올로보다 훨씬 나아
You are so much better for me
than Paolo ever was.
날 걱정해 주고 사랑해 주고
웃겨 주고...
You care about me, you're loving,
you make me laugh.
웃겨 줄 얘기가 또 있어
If I make you laugh, here's an idea.
파올로를 불러서
침대에서 뒹굴어
Invite Paolo to have
a romp in the sack...
...and I'll stand in the corner
and tell knock-knock jokes!
난 구석에서 웃긴 얘기나 할게
로스!
너와 나는 특별한 사이야
파올로와는...
What we have is special!
All Paolo and I ever had was
동물적인 결합이었다고?
"Animal sex"?
그러니까 네 말은 우리 사이는
전혀 동물적이지 않다는 거지?
So what are you saying?
There's nothing between us
"animal" at all?
조그만 동물 같은 것도...
다람쥐만큼도 안 된단 거지?
There's not even,
like, a little animal?
Not even, like...
...chipmunk sex?
좋아, 로스
내 말 잘 들어, 응?
Try to hear me, okay?
I'm not gonna lie to you.
솔직하게 말해 줄게
파올로와는 잘지냈어
-lt was good with Paolo.
-Knock-knock.
- 웃긴 얘기는...
- 하지만
너랑 나는 더 잘지내잖아
But what you and I have
is so much better.
우리는 서로 사랑하고
애정도 있고 친밀해
We have tenderness,
we have intimacy, we connect.
맹세해, 내가 경험한 것 중에
지금이 최고야
You know? I swear.
This is the best...
... I have ever had.
최고는 지금부터야
Until now.
- 안녕
리차드가 날 사랑한대
Richard told me he loved me.
- 그래?
- 그래
-Oh, my God!
-I know!
너무 잘됐다!
Honey, that's great!
I know!
- 그게 어디 있더라?
- 위 서랍에 있어
-I just can't find
-Top drawer.
-Hurry.
-Why? You need one too?
- 너도 필요하니?
- 으응
찾았다!
Found them!
하나밖에 없어
There's only one.
모니카!
곧 갈게요
결정할 일이 있거든요
We'll be right there.
We're just trying to decide something.
레이첼?
- 박사님?
- 응?
- 결정할 일이 있다는군
- 좋죠!
-They're trying to decide something.
-Good. Good, good.
콧수염 말인데요
예전에는 달랐나요?
So was your mustache
Did it used to be different?
아니
어떻게 그렇게
깔끔하게 다듬어요?
How do you, you know,
keep it so neat?
작은 빗이 있거든
I have a comb.
뭐라고 부르는데요?
-What is that?
-A mustache comb.
- 콧수염 빗
- 고맙습니다
Thank you.
한 달 동안 네 빨래 해줄게
Okay, I will do your laundry
for one month.
- 싫어
- 좋아, 알았어!
I will, I will, I will....
그러면 내가...
청소 다 할게, 두 달 동안
I will clean the apartment
for two months.
I'll give this to you now, if you
tell me where we keep the dustpan.
좋아, 너한테 줄게
네가 쓰레기통을 맡아
베트남 전에 참전했어요?
So were you in Nam?
- 가위 바위 보 할래?
- 좋아
-Rock, paper, scissors?
-Gotcha.
- 가위, 바위, 보!
- 됐어!
One, two, three.
Yes!
Fine. Go have sex.
- 좋아, 가서 잘해 봐
- 고마워
아냐, 자네는 완전히
잘못 알고 있어
No! You have got it completely wrong!
John Savage was Deer Hunter,
no legs.
'디어 헌터'의 존 세비지는
다리가 없었고
'귀향'의 존 보이트는
다리가 마비였어
Jon Voight was Coming Home,
couldn't feel his legs.
말도 안 돼요
당신이 잘못 알고 있어요
You've got it totally the other way
around, my friend. Jon Voight
- 존 보이트는...
- 자기?
-Honey?
-What?
Shall we?
- 자야지?
- 안 될 것 같아요
It's not gonna happen.
오늘은 저쪽이 하고
우리는 내일이에요
They're doing it tonight.
We can do it tomorrow.
다음에는 스케줄을
미리 알려 주겠어?
In the future, if I could see
the schedule beforehand....
아침에 일어나 보니까
신발 깔창을 훔쳐갔더라고
So when I woke up this morning...
... he'd stolen all the insoles
out of my shoes!
Why?
왜?
자기 옛 여자친구랑 자고
물고기를 죽였다고
He thinks I slept with his
ex-girlfriend and killed his fish.
그걸 왜 죽였는데?
Why would you kill his fish?
때론 말야, 피비
누군가랑 자고 난 후...
Because sometimes
after you sleep with someone...
물고기를 죽여야 하기도 해
...you have to kill a fish.
챈들러, 정말 힘들겠다
Chandler, honey...
... I'm sorry.
어서 조이의 드라마를 틀어 봐!
Can we watch Joey's show now, please?
- 그래
- 아직 조이가 안 왔잖아
Wait. He's not here yet.
- 출연자가 내용을 봐서 뭐해?
- 맞다
He knows what happens.
내 문제는 다 해결된 거구나?
I'm fine about my problem now,
by the way.
앰버, 내가 항상 당신 곁에
있다는 걸 알아줬으면 해
Amber...
...I'll always be there for you...
친구로서, 오빠로서 말이야
...as a friend and as your brother.
드레이크!
Oh, Drake.
기운 내요
상도 못 타고 앰버까지...
Hard day, huh?
First the medical award, now this?
그러게 말이에요
누구는 참 운도 좋죠
Some guys are just lucky, I guess.
라모레 박사님
1층 응급실로 와 주세요
Dr. Ramoray, report to
first floor Emergency stat.
올 게 왔군
Well, then...
... I guess that's me.
누구 같이 탈 사람?
자네는? 윌 박사님은요?
Anyone else need to go on the elevator?
Dr. Horton? Dr. Wall?
자네만 불렀다구
They only said you.
알았어, 알았다고
Oh, okay. All right.
I love you.
사랑해요, 드레이크
그러거나 말거나
Yeah, whatever.
- 안 돼
- 드레이크!
Oh, no!
Drake, look out!
- 지금 조이가 죽은 거야?
- 설마!
-Did they just kill off Joey?
-No!
그런가 봐
Now maybe.
조이, 문 열어
할 말 있어
Come on! Open up!
We want to talk to you!
말할 기분이 아냐!
I don't feel like talking!
- 조이, 걱정돼서 그래
- 네 걱정을 하고 있다고
Come on! We care about you.
-We're worried about you.
-And some of us really have to pee!
누가 오줌 마렵대!
I'm sorry, Joey.
미안해, 조이
널 죽이다니
정말 웃기지도 않아
Listen, sorry about your death.
That really sucks.
- 보자마자 달려왔어
- 왜 말 안 했어?
-We came over as soon as we saw.
-How could you not tell us?
I don't know. I was kind of hoping
no one would ever find out.
모르겠어
아무도 보지 않길 바랬나 봐
Well, maybe they could find
a way to bring you back.
다시 널 살려 줄지도 모르잖아
아니, 대본에 시체를 찾았는데
머리가 박살이 났대
They said that when they found my body,
my brain was so smashed in...
뇌 전문가는 나밖에 없잖아
...that the only doctor
who could've saved me was me.
정말 아이러니하지 않니?
It's supposed to be
some kind of irony.
조이, 걱정 마
세상 끝난 건 아니잖아
But Joey, you're gonna be fine.
You don't need that show.
It was just a dumb soap opera.
정말 바보 같은 드라마였어
피비, 나한테는 그 드라마가
최고의 경험이었어
This was the greatest thing
that ever happened to me.
맞아, 그 말은 취소할게
Yes! I was going to incorporate that.
모니카가 조언을 해줄 거야
Here's Monica.
She'll have something nice to say.
I straightened out your shower curtain
so you won't get mildew.
샤워 커튼을 정리해 놨으니까
곰팡이 걱정은 없을 거야
왜? 나라면 힘이 될 거야
What? To me, that's nice.
- 괜찮을 거야, 언제나처럼
- 아니, 안 그래
It'll be okay. You know that.
No, I don't.
이건 마치... 일생 동안
뭔가를 위해 일했다고 쳐
It's like you work
your whole life for something...
...and you think
that when you get it...
어느 정도 됐다고 안심하는데
허사가 될 상황이 터진 거야
...it'll never be
as good as you thought.
But this so was.
얼마나 타격이 큰지 몰라
It changed everything.
Like, the other day,
I got this credit card application...
어제까지만 해도 내 신분은
확실했어, 누구나 알아줬다구
...and I was pre-approved!
그전 같으면 사람들이
내가 누군지 알기나 했냐?
I've never been pre-approved
for anything in my life!
정말 유감이다
I'm sorry, man.
I don't know if this'll mean
anything to you...
조이, 다른 사람들은 몰라도
우린 네 진가를 인정하고 있어
... but you'll always be
pre-approved with us.
그건 내게 아무런 의미도 없어
That means nothing to me.
피칸 쿠키 먹을래?
방금 만들었어
Pecan sandy? Just made them.
먹지 뭐
Yeah, all right.
Are these raisins?
이건 건포도야?
그럼 뭐겠어?
Sure, why not?
이봐, 에디...
Listen, Eddie.
우리가 함께 사는 거 말야...
I've been thinking about
our living situation.
왜 웃지?
Why are you smiling?
놀래 줄 게 있어
새 금붕어야
I got a little surprise.
Look. There's a new fishy.
이름은 챈들러
네 이름을 땄어
I named him...
... Chandler, you know, after you.
금붕어가 아닌데?
Well, that's not even a real fish.
금붕어 크래커잖아
No, that's a Goldfish cracker.
So what's your point, man?
그래서 뭐?
알았어, 잘 자
Okay, good night.
이 변태 같은 녀석아
You big freak of nature!
- 안녕하세요
- 안녕
- 날씨 좋지?
- 네
-Brisk tonight.
-Oh, man.
-Let's never speak of this.
-You got it.
- 더 이상 말하지 말자고
- 좋죠